Listen, laugh, and learn every single day right here on The Amanda Seals Show and on our podcast.
Just search The Amanda Seals Show, wherever you get your podcast.
And let's talk about Amanda Seals' other podcast.
It's called Small Doses.
Amanda, this week, the episode is called Side Effects of Parenting.
Now, that topic could go in any direction.
No, Side Effects of Parents.
Side Effects of Parents.
Very different, very different.
I mean, that could be in any direction.
What did you actually talk about in this episode?
So the reason why I need to give the distinction is because if we say Side Effects of Parenting,
then people think that's what we're talking about is going to be raising children.
That's what people will think we're talking about.
When I talk about Side Effects of Parents, what I'm talking about in this episode is the relationship between adults and their parents.
And that's a whole different dynamic.
And it was really a dope interview.
I mean, it wasn't an interview.
It was a dope episode for me to do because I've been having my own journey with me and my mother.
And so a lot of times on the podcast becomes kind of like therapeutic where I get to get stuff off my chest.
So every Monday when I'm recording the episodes, I'll go on Instagram and I'll say,
Hey, today we're recording Side Effects of blah, blah, blah.
You know, drop your questions in the comments.
And one of the questions that people asked was,
Why is it that mothers raise their daughters but love their sons?
You got to listen to the episode to find out the reason.